The only way to save the one you love, is to die.
Charlie Countryman is a action, comedy, drama film directed by Fredrik Bond.
A young American falls hard for a Romanian cellist whose father has recently
died -- and whose violent past could bring about his own demise.
Charlie Countryman, played by Shia LaBeouf.
Gabi Ibanescu, played by Evan Rachel Wood.
Nigel, played by Mads Mikkelsen.
Darko, played by Til Schweiger.
Carl, played by Rupert Grint.
Luc, played by James Buckley.
Charlie Countryman (originally titled The Necessary Death of Charlie Countryman as well as Kill Charlie Countryman) is a 2013 romantic drama film
directed by Fredrik Bond in his directorial debut, written by Matt Drake, and starring Shia LaBeouf, Evan Rachel Wood and Mads Mikkelsen.
The film premiered on January 21, 2013 at the 2013 Sundance Film Festival and was
screened in competition at the 63rd Berlin International Film Festival.
The film was released November 15, 2013 in the United States was
released on October 31, 2014 in the United Kingdom.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.